theattractionforums.com 2017-12-12

# Privacy Policy | Theattractionforums.com

Privacy Policy

What information does Love Systems collect from our users and how do we collect it? Love Systems only contacts individuals who specifically request that we do so or in the event that they have signed up to receive our free newsletters or have purchased one of our products. Love Systems collects personally identifying information from our users during online registration and online purchasing. Generally, this information includes name and e-mail address for registration to receive our free newsletters and name, postal address, and credit card information when purchasing our products. All of this information is provided to us by you. How do we use this information? This information is used for internal marketing purposes only. Love Systems does not sell, exchange, or release your personal information (name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit data, etc.) Your information is not shared with any other third party or company outside of billing and shipping purposes.

What are cookies and how do we use them? Cookies help track a person's "session" while online. By showing how and when our visitors use this site, this information can help us to continue to improve our site. We will only use cookies to view information on your hard drive that was put there by a cookie from this site. The use of cookies is an industry standard and many web sites use them. Cookies are stored on your computer and not on this site. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so, if your browser so permits. How do we store your information? Your information is stored at the list server that delivers Love Systems newsletters. Your information can only be accessed by those who help manage those lists in order to deliver e-mail to those who would like to receive Love System's newsletters.

All of the newsletters that are sent to you by Love Systems include an unsubscribe link in them. You can remove yourself at any time from our newsletters by clicking on the unsubscribe link. You can also contact us at [info@lovesystems.com](mailto:info@lovesystems.com) to change your information at any time. Disclaimer: This policy may be changed at any time at Love System's discretion. If we should update this policy, we will post the updates to this page on our website. This policy was revised September 24, 2009.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy please direct them to [info@lovesystems.com](mailto:info@lovesystems.com). You may also send a letter to:

Love Systems  
Unit 900, 901 King St W  
Toronto, ON  
M5V-3H5

Our site is hosted by ZeroLag Communications which can be reached at 1-877-ZERO-LAG with offices located at:

289 S. Robertson Blvd #441  
Beverly Hills, CA 90211  
United States
